const additionalServices = [
    {
      icon: Shield,
      title: "Counterfeit Medication Awareness",
      description: "Education and partnerships to help identify and prevent counterfeit medication use.",
      details: "We provide comprehensive education about identifying counterfeit medications and partner with healthcare providers to ensure medication safety."
    },
    {
      icon: Heart,
      title: "Cardiovascular Health Education",
      description: "Awareness, prevention, and education programs focused on heart health and cardiovascular wellness.",
      details: "Our cardiovascular programs include heart health screenings, education about risk factors, and prevention strategies for heart disease."
    },
    {
      icon: Brain,
      title: "Progress Assessment and Tracking",
      description: "Comprehensive monitoring and evaluation of participant progress and program effectiveness.",
      details: "At Ma AluTheresia Memory Rescue and Glitter of Hope Health Inc., we track participant progress and outcomes through a base admission tool and follow-up questionnaires, ensuring our programs are effective and beneficial."
    }
  ];
