  const additionalServices = [
    {
      icon: Shield,
      title: "Counterfeit Medication Awareness",
      description: "Education and partnerships to help identify and prevent counterfeit medication use.",
      details: "We provide comprehensive education about identifying counterfeit medications and partner with healthcare providers to ensure medication safety."
    },
    {
      icon: Heart,
      title: "Cardiovascular Health Education",
      description: "Awareness, prevention, and education programs focused on heart health and cardiovascular wellness.",
      details: "Our cardiovascular programs include education about risk factors, early signs of heart attack, heart failure, hypertension, stroke, and other related conditions, as well as prevention strategies for heart disease, promoting overall cardiovascular wellness through holistic approaches."
    },
    {
      icon: Brain,
      title: "Progress Assessment and Tracking",
      description: "Comprehensive monitoring and evaluation of participant progress and program effectiveness.",
      details: "At Ma AluTheresia Memory Rescue and Glitter of Hope Health Inc., we track participant progress and outcomes through a base admission tool and follow-up questionnaires, ensuring our programs are effective and beneficial."
    }
  ];
