    },
    {
      icon: Brain,
      title: "Progress Assessment and Tracking",
      description: "Comprehensive monitoring and evaluation of participant progress and program effectiveness.",
      details: "At Ma AluTheresia Memory Rescue and Glitter of Hope Health Inc., we track participant progress and outcomes through a base admission tool and follow-up questionnaires, ensuring our programs are effective and beneficial."
    }
